One disappearance, one murder.
See eon ee eee ee
Coy ee et ten eae a Ty
Same place, 8 weeks before the election
Crane en eee oie
x
CSE etn ante LCi ie
Same place, 8 weeks before the election
Minister of Justice Gunnar tlvestad.
Minister of Justice Gunnar Elvestad.
pn aan ORC SL Ce
eum iene
pure cea an SO SD Ce
eae cas
eters CREM
Ceara aaa
Pacer] we Crates v v
Ceo Rarer '
At least rw ents '
Rae ie eens
PaO LET
of nae 3 a
ares
STE an (eet ale aa cocad
emery et eae
POSE me eeecem Le aa ead
one rsv Ire erase
Some ecco Le an ead
ener c Ire etter
SCE accom ae ead
rae SCTE ettssa a
Cee eres tes
ROS een aa tees
pean Re cen sare mee erated aes
Pn eSo eer ea teen
Peace ee
Poa eee ae
Reese ee
Pe eee ae
Pea ete eee
VaR cet reRoae cer gst
here because I want you to be?
How do you know you aren't
SOROS c Cr is
here because L want you to be?
How do you know you aren't
ACR Me en ol EC
PCRS re Pete Cg
Alesse eo eg
PIC et RR nee re eet Nia
ACOs MSS ee or CLS
Twa LR anes re CeCe in
ACU e Ca eer eS
Pe Ree re ere te ng
Pret aie
Se ses eC eT
- Out with it!
Bee Lp cece oe
Bal Seana
+ ¥ trusted you. It's all been lies.
Soran)
eer. Re Cee Ue
Soon we'll be living in the
eee a ST cee Sees
Cre a em) PAY
Noe ce eer
reg eeree Ce MR
Ree RRL LTy
Ce eet a ed
UN ee Tene ee SLL
Err)
United
ST eC)
Cue
SAPO thinks Neo-Nazis
Peet mtn ted
A
yee Lew Coan ric
are behind the murders.
SAPO thinks Neo-Nazis
Pee MO eee
cree
ae %
ty \ ie my}
.
x Sens
“wh Det yt aia
“>.
I could have stopped it.
See Ee Tere
per creas
cae teeter a
Sarasota re aL ese
above its citizens.
The state has placed itself
Breen ema cPscn eS
BD oaee eos
ene nia
Leet
arene ce
That's over now.
Today we take up arms.
Be San
NaN et Ge
AG aee tre meta
re eee